$ocum_header_main_settings	Main OCum Settings
$ocum_header_adjustments	Adjustments
$ocum_header_reset	Reset Options
$ocum_header_ocum_inflated	OCum Inflated
$ocum_option_clean_water_enter	Clean cum when character enters water
$ocum_option_disable_cum_shots	Disable cum shots
$ocum_option_disable_cum_decals	Disable cum decals
$ocum_option_disable_cum_meshes	Disable cum meshes
$ocum_option_disable_cum_inflation	Disable cum inflation
$ocum_option_disable_facials_elins	Disable facials for Tera Elin race actors
$ocum_option_cum_regen_speed	Cum Regeneration Speed
$ocum_option_squirt_chance	Squirt chance
$ocum_option_cum_cleanup_timer	Cum cleanup time (in real life minutes)
$ocum_option_inflation_cleanup_timer	Inflation cleanup time (in real life minutes)
$ocum_option_cum_bar_key	Show cum bar key
$ocum_option_realistic_cum_mode	Enable realistic cum application mode
$ocum_option_clean_cum_decals	Clean cum decals from all actors
$ocum_option_clear_inflation	Clear inflation from all actors
$ocum_option_reset_defaults	Reset all options to defaults
$ocum_option_enable_higher_cum_regen_speed	Enable higher cum regen speed
$ocum_option_enable_deleveled_cum_bar_npcs	Enable deleveled cum storage for male NPCs
$ocum_option_enable_deleveled_cum_bar_player	Enable deleveled cum storage for male Player
$ocum_option_cum_bar_max_amount_npcs	Male NPC max cum storage
$ocum_option_cum_bar_max_amount_player	Male player character max cum storage
$ocum_option_enable_fixed_uterine_volume_npcs	Enable fixed uterine volume for female NPCs
$ocum_option_uterine_volume_npcs	Female NPC uterine volume
$ocum_option_enable_fixed_uterine_volume_player	Enable fixed uterine volume for female Player
$ocum_option_uterine_volume_player	Female Player uterine volume
$ocum_option_max_belly_size	Max size
$ocum_option_body_morph	Body Morph
$ocum_option_cum_spurts	Cum spurts
$ocum_option_always_fill_to_max	Always fill to max
$ocum_message_box_option_yes	Yes
$ocum_message_box_option_no	No
$ocum_highlight_clean_water_enter	Sets whether cum textures are cleaned when characters enter water. Note that when you change this option, it only takes effect on cummed characters after the option is changed. Characters that already have cum in them will not be affected, unless they are cummed on again.
$ocum_highlight_disable_cum_shots	Enable or disable cumshots. These are the projectiles that come out of the schlong on orgasm. Does not affect cum texture application.
$ocum_highlight_disable_cum_decals	Enable or disable cum decals. These are the textures that are applied to the body, face, feet and hands on orgasm.
$ocum_highlight_disable_cum_meshes	Enable or disable cum meshes. Cum meshes are 3D cum effects. They might not look good on very thick bodies. Cum application might look excessive when used together with cum decals. Cum meshes do NOT stay on after OStim scenes end, as they are an equippable item like an armour.
$ocum_highlight_disable_cum_inflation	Enable or disable cum inflation. This is the belly inflation that occurs after a female actor is overfilled with cum. Note that you need HUGE amounts of cum for this effect to apply. Usually only possible with very high level characters.
$ocum_highlight_cum_regen_speed	Set how fast cum regenerates for male characters. This is a multiplier value between 0.1 and 10. If it is set to 2, it means it regenerates twice as fast as default.
$ocum_highlight_squirt_chance	Sets the probability of female squirting on orgasm. 100 means she will always squirt on every orgasm.
$ocum_highlight_cum_cleanup_timer	Set how long it takes for cum textures to disappear from characters who have cum on them. This value is in real life minutes. Note that when you change this option, it only takes effect on characters that are cummed on after the option is changed.
$ocum_highlight_inflation_cleanup_timer	Set how long it takes for cum inflation to be cleared from characters whose belly is inflated or starting to be inflated by cum. This value is in real life minutes. Note that when you change this option, it only takes effect on characters that are inflated after the option is changed.
$ocum_highlight_cum_bar_key	Set which key displays the cum bar. Set to Esc to disable it.
$ocum_highlight_realistic_cum_mode	Enabling this option will apply only reasonable or more realistic amounts of cum, independent of character level. For instance, if you cum inside the vagina, cum textures might not be applied on the body. Enable this if you think the cum application is too excessive.
$ocum_highlight_clean_cum_decals	Click this option to clean cum textures from all characters who currently have applied. For emergency in case cum doesn't clean off by normal means, or if you simply want to reset cum textures which were applied.
$ocum_highlight_clear_inflation	Click this option to clear inflation from all characters who currently have inflation (even if the effect is not yet noticeable). For emergency in case belly inflation isn't removed by normal means, or if you simply want to remove belly inflation from characters who currently have it.
$ocum_highlight_disable_facials_elins	Sets whether facial cum textures will be disabled for Tera Elin actors or not. Tera Elin race uses different head maps than the normal races, so the facial textures may not look good. Enable this option if you don't like the facials on Elin characters.
$ocum_highlight_enable_higher_cum_regen_speed	Enable this option to be able to select higher cum regen speeds in the cum regen slider below (up to 50x)
$ocum_highlight_enable_develed_cum_bar_npcs	Enable this option so that Male NPCs have a deleveled cum bar (max cum stored is always the same regardless of level). Adjust the male NPCs max cum storage in the slider option below.
$ocum_highlight_enable_develed_cum_bar_player	Enable this option so that Male Player Character has a deleveled cum bar (max cum stored is always the same regardless of level). Adjust the male Player Character max cum storage in the slider option below. This option will NOT do anything if your character is Female.
$ocum_highlight_cumbar_max_amount	For reference:\nLevel 1 has 3 mL max cum storage\nLevel 25 has 27 mL max cum storage\nLevel 50 has 52 mL max cum storage\nLevel 100 has 102 mL max cum storage
$ocum_highlight_enable_fixed_uterine_volume_npcs	Uterine volume is random for each NPC by default. Enable this option to set a fixed value instead. Set the value in the slider option below.
$ocum_highlight_enable_fixed_uterine_volume_player	Uterine volume is random for player character by default. Enable this option to set a fixed value instead. Set the value in the slider option below. This option will NOT do anything if your character is Male.
$ocum_highlight_uterine_volume_npcs	The higher the value, the more difficult it is to trigger belly inflation effect.
$ocum_highlight_uterine_volume_player	The higher the value, the more difficult it is to trigger belly inflation effect.
$ocum_highlight_max_belly_size	Set maximum size of the selected body morph from cum inflation.
$ocum_highlight_body_morph	Set the body morph for cum inflation. The default is PregnancyBelly
$ocum_highlight_cum_spurts	Set the amount of cum spurts for the inflation animation. Setting this to 1 will make the inflation smooth and continuous.
$ocum_highlight_always_fill_to_max	Always inflate the female actor fully no matter what.
$ocum_message_cum_cleaned	Cum decals have been cleaned from all actors.
$ocum_message_inflation_cleaned	Cum inflation has been cleared from all actors.
$ocum_message_defaults_reset	All options have been reset to their defaults.
$ocum_message_cum_meshes_warning	You have enabled cum meshes. THEY BREAK OAHEGAO IF YOU ARE PLAYING A FEMALE CHARACTER, AND ALSO RESET FACIAL EXPRESSIONS WHEN THE CUM MESHES ARE APPLIED! If you use any version of OAhegao, please disable cum meshes! Ignore this warning if you don't use OAhegao or if you play a Male character.
